Check, charge or cash?
支票、信用卡还是现金？
Cash.
现金
Make it out to...
发票写…
...Jack's Demolition. Tucson.
土珊市积氏拆卸公司
$788.30.
总数788.30元
Taking me to breakfast?
和我吃早餐吗？
I can't. I'm meeting Bosko.
我见博高
Hey, Vincent.
云信
Where are my barrettes?
我的发夹呢？
I saw them on the kitchen table.
我看见在桌上
I already checked.
我看过了
Coffee?
咖啡？
No school today?
今天不用上学？
My dad's taking me to the new building and then to lunch.
爸爸带我去新大厦然后吃午餐
Try under the sofa cushions.
到沙发垫子下找
He's already a half an hour late.
他迟了半小时
He's going to show, or stand her up like last time?
他会出现还是像上次那样爽约？
I'll make coffee.
我煮咖啡
Out of time.
没时间了
Mom, my barrettes are not on the couch.
我的发夹不在椅上
Wear the blue ones.
戴蓝色那一个
I don't want to wear the blue ones. They don't match.
我不想戴，颜色不配衬
- Did you check in your bathroom? - I checked everywhere!
浴室找过没有？ 找过了
What do you want me to do?
我该怎办？
Find them!
去找！
- Mom, pay attention! - All right, sweetie, all right!
妈，留心！
Daddy's going to be here.
爸爸会到来
I won't be ready!
我来不及准备
- I'll be late. - No, you won't.
我会迟到
I will be late!
我会迟的
Before Daddy comes, we can find them if we look together.
若一起找爸到来前会找到
It's all right, baby. It's all right.
没事的，宝贝
We'll find them together, you and me. We'll find them.
我们一起找
Just relaX. He won't come before we find them. I promise you.
放心，他到来前我们会找到
Give me another refill.
给我添一杯
What's your name?
你叫什么？
Waingro.
荣谷
You're Michael?
你是米高？
You guys always work together?
你们常一起合作？
All the time.
经常合作
Real tight crew?
合作无间？
Real tight.
是的
If this works good, I'd consider going again, you know.
若今次顺利，我会考虑再做
Yeah. Stop talking, okay, Slick?
好的，别再说话，滑头
How's he doing?
他怎样？
Hundred percent.
百份百满意
Right on schedule.
很准时
Made a right on Venice Boulevard.
威尼斯街右转
We're a mile and a half from you.
我们离你一里半
Okay.
好
Just crossed over the number one lane, 300 yards from you.
越过行车快线离你三百码
Get set.
准备
I am.
准备好
Here we go.
行动
211!We're being held up!
有劫案！我们遇劫
- 211 alarm. Armored car. - There's the call.
装甲车遇劫 已通知了警方
Three minutes.
有三分钟
Clear!
离开！
Eighty seconds left!
只剩80秒
Get back! Get back!
退后！
Slick, see that shit coming out of their ears? They can't fucking hear you!
滑头，他耳朵流血，听不到的
Cool it!
别胡来
I got it.
找到了
Got it.
到手
You had to fuck with me.
你要和我过不去
Want to fuck with me?
和我过不去？
What are you doing? What did he do?
他做什么？
He was making a move.
他作势要攻击
Dumb motherfucker.
狗娘养的
A million siX...
160万
Forty cents on the dollar, $640,000 to you.
每元分4角，你可得64万
Here's $150,000 front money.
这是15万的预支
Get you the rest in two, three days.
其余的两三天后付
Who owned these?
是谁拥有的？
"Malibu Equity and Investments."
马莉堡股票及投资公司
Roger Van Zant.
罗杰宏山…
Owns banks in the Caymans...
在开曼群岛拥有银行…
...runs investment portfolios for offshore drug money. Stuff like that.
替国外贩毒的钱负责投资事务
So?
那么？
You ripped off his bearer bonds.
你偷了他的债券
He's insured.
他买了保险
That's the point. He collects 100 percent from the insurance.
他可获百份百的保险赔偿
He's a player. Maybe he buys his bonds back from us...
也许他向我们购回债券…
...for 60 percent of their value. Makes 40 percent on top of the 100 percent.
六折价购回，再赚四成
Sell it back to him, that's an eXtra $320,000 to you.
债券卖给他你可再得32万
Try it on.
试试看
Kelso called.
祈素来电话
About what?
关于什么事？
A score he's putting out, he wants you to look at.
他找人参与买卖
I don't need his score. I got my own.
我不需要，我自己有买卖
Says it's clean and low eight figures.
说钱无法追查而且过千万元
9:00 a.m. Tomorrow.
明天九时
What happened?
发生什么事？
Don't ask.
别问了
Find the ambulance?
找到救伤车吗？
- Dumped it four blocks from here. - 22nd Street.
在四条街外遭弃掉
They torched it. Burned the guns, clothes, everything.
纵火烧掉，枪和衣服化为灰烬
They were airborne. They taped the last few seconds of the black-and-whites.
记者在上半拍下几秒的黑白片
Stolen from Fresno two weeks ago.
救伤车两星期前被偷
Yellow pickup truck out of Whittier a day before yesterday.
黄色车是前天在惠帝尔被偷
You taking this one?
你负责此案？
Or does it stay in Division?
还是由分局调查？
Does this look like gangbangers working the local 7-11 to you?
这一宗是便利店劫案吗？
Robbery-Homicide's taking it.
抢劫及凶杀组接手调查
We got three motorists.
三名司机目击事发
All they saw were men with masks. They were distant.
只看见戴上面罩的人
TV man over there, however, he was closer.
那边的电视汉子较近现场
Did he ID anybody?
他认出任何人吗？
He was hiding. He heard it mostly.
他躲起来，听到大部份对话
What about them?
他们呢？
According to TV man, this guy started mouthing off.
电视汉说这人在胡言乱语
Smart.
很聪明
Somebody called a guard "Slick."
有人叫护卫做“滑头”
Now, I figure this guy...
我认为此人…
...went for that hold-out piece, ankle holster.
想拿绑在足踝的枪
From here...
由这儿…
...bang, bang...bang, bang, bang.
开枪…
This side.
子弹由这儿穿出
This guy has got what appears to be a double tap-entry wound to the sternum.
这人看来似是胸部中枪
Tattooing around the head wound, scorched bones, close range.Probably eXecuted.
从头的伤势看似是近距离被杀
It was a million siX in bearer bonds.
160万的债券被盗
They ignored the loose cash.
他们没拿走现金
'Cause they had no time. They were on a clock.
他们没时间，时间紧迫
Which means they knew our response time to a 211...
他们知道警方何时会到达
...had our air, immobilized it, entered...
听警方广播，把车截停，进入…
...escaped in under three minutes.
及在三分钟内逃走
It's a good spot here. We got good escape routes.
这是好地点，有良好逃走路线
Two freeways...
两条公路…
...within a quarter of a mile.
在四分一里之内
Traffic video camera?
交通录影
Probably disabled. Check it anyway.
可能给弄坏了，但查看一下
You recognize the M. O?
你认出手法吗？
M. O...
手法…
...is that they're good.
是职业劫匪所为
Once it escalated into a murder-one beef for all, after they killed two guards...
他们杀两警卫犯了一级谋杀罪…
...they didn't hesitate.
之后便不再迟疑
Popped guard number three because... what difference does it make?
杀第三名，因为横竖也是犯罪
Why leave a living witness?
为何留下证人呢？
Drop of a hat, these guys will rock-and-roll.
他们会毫不迟疑，心狠手辣
The shape charge.
定向炸药
The shape charge indicates that they are technically proficient.
显示劫匪的技术是精通的
Proficient enough to go in on the prowl.
足以使他们在途中下手
Let's look for recent high-line burglaries that mystify us.
我们要找偷值钱东西的劫匪
Run "Slick" as an alias to the FBI. You're gonna get the phone book.
查“滑头”这绰号名单可能很长
Do it anyway. Who's moving the bearer bonds?
但还要查，谁卖出债券？
Check the usual fences. You and I will check Cuzomano and Torena.
查惯常接赃者，你和我查古和陶
I want you to take Goldstein and Alfaro.
我要你查高士丹及艾化鲁
Hang in with Forensics.
和鉴证科紧密合作
From the bomb squad, I want the eXplosive.
向炸弹组查问用的是什么炸药
If we're lucky, it's eXotic. We can trace the sale.
若是罕见的，可追查发售来源
Get your hand out of that man's pocket.
你别伸手进那人的口袋
Anyone want some pie?
有谁要吃批饼？
Gotta go to the john.
我要上厕所
I had to get it on. He was making a move. I had to get it on.
他作势攻击我要先下手为强
Split's in the car. I took out of ours evenly...
他那份在车上，我们的均分了…
...to make up for his full end...
以便全数给他…
...'cause I want to pay off and get rid of this motherfucker right now.
因我想立即分给和打发这杂种
Hold it!
等一等
Where's the rest?
其余的钱呢？
We're late. You look too good to go out.
时候不早了，你打扮得很漂亮
I'll just jump you right here.
我想在这儿和你做爱
- Where is it? - Squared the bookies, baby.
钱呢？ 还给外围马的人
There's more in a couple of days, so don't sweat it. We're late.
几天后还会有钱，放心吧
Come on.
少胡说
You gotta be kidding me.
你定是说笑
Honey...
亲爱的…
...it ain't worth the risks you take for $8,000. Like in "Risk versus reward."
为区区八千元值得冒这个险吗？
Let's go.
走吧
Get your coat.
拿你的外衣
There is no point talking. You're a child growing older.
无谓再说，你心智还没成熟
What does that mean?
什么意思？
We're not making forward progress like real grown-up adults living our lives...
我们不像成年人那样有进步…
...because I married a gambling junkie.
因为我嫁给一个赌徒
Get in the fucking car.
上车吧
What am I doing in here?
我怎可以这样下去的？
You're not!
你不用！
You want me to leave the bank book and the car keys...
你离开这里时留下…
...in the kitchen on the way out the door?
银行存折和车匙
- Are we going? - Keep that crap. Dominick comes with me.
你留着吧，我带多明走
Don't even think about...
你别妄想…
Tell me Albert Torena called back.
陶亚拔覆电话了
Albert Torena call Vincent?
陶亚拔有给云信电话吗？
No.
没有
Report came in.
有报告
The explosive was Dy-Ex, used in demolition.
炸药是拆毁用的…
You can pick it up in Nevada...
可在内华达…
...Arizona, New MeXico.
亚利桑拿、新墨西哥州买到
Too common to trace a sale.
太普通难以追查来源
That's wonderful.
那太好了
You all right?
你没事吧？
What happened? Where have you been?
怎么了？你去了哪儿？
Work.
工作
Lauren's dad show up?
罗兰的父亲有来吗？
Didn't call...
没来电话…
...didn't show. We waited for you till 10:30.
没出现，我们等你直至十时半
Now, does this guy have any idea what's going on with this kid?
这人知道他女儿是怎样的吗？
I don't know.
我不知道
Fucking jerk.
该死的混蛋
Is she okay?
她没事吧？
She's been in her room all day.
她整天在房内
So, no, she's not okay. Neither am I.
她有事，我亦不开心
I made dinner...
我弄了晚餐…
...for us, four hours ago.
四小时前为我们煮了
Every time I try to maintain a consistent mood between us...
我设法替我们保持一贯的情绪
...you withdraw.
你退却了
I got three dead bodies on a sidewalk...
在威尼斯大道旁边…
...off Venice Boulevard, Justine.
躺着三名死者，彩钿
I'm sorry...
对不起…
...if the goddamn...
若那可恶的…
...chicken...
鸡…
...got overcooked.
给煮过了头
Coffee, sir?
要咖啡吗？
Please.
好的
Will you pass the cream?
请把奶递给我
Thanks.
谢谢
What'd you get?
你买了什么？
What?
什么？
What are you reading?
你看什么书？
Book about metals.
关于金属的书
Stress Fractures in Titanium.
钛的应力折断
What kind of work do you do?
你做什么的？
Lady, why are you so interested in what I read or what I do?
你为何对我看什么书感兴趣？
I've seen you in the store.
我在店中看见你
What store?
什么店？
Hennessey and Ingalls. I work there.
我在书店工作
If you don't want to talk to me, it's okay.
若你不想交谈，好的
I'm sorry I bothered you.
抱歉打扰了你
I didn't mean to be rude. I didn't recognize you.
我不想无礼，只是认不出你
I work in metals. I'm a salesman.
我是营业员，专营金属的
My name's Neil.
我叫尼尔
I'm Eady.
我叫伊荻
You like working there?
你喜欢在书店工作？
Sure.
是的
I get a discount and there's a whole section of books in my area.
我买书有折扣亦有我行内的书
What area?
是哪一行业？
Graphic design.
平面设计
I do letterheads and logotypes at night and...
晚上设计信纸及商标…
...the store's a day job until I get enough going.
白天在书店工作直至能藉此谋生
Who do you do that for?
你为谁设计呢？
A restaurant.
餐厅
I did their menus, and...
我设计他们的餐牌，以及…
...a small record label.
为小唱片公司设计
CDs.
镭射唱片封套
I've done two so far.
目前已设计了两张
You go to school for that?
你上学校受训吗？
Yeah.
是的
I went to Parsons.
我念过巴桑学校
Where's that?
在哪儿？
New York City.
纽约市
How long you been here?
你在这儿住了多久？
About a year.
约一年
Like it?
喜欢这儿吗？
Not really. I'm mostly here for the work.
不算喜欢，我为工作才来这儿
Live in this neighborhood?
你住在附近？
No, I live kind of above Sunset Plaza.
不，我住在日落广场上面山上
It's a little house I rent.
租住一所小房子
And it's kind of rundown, but a beautiful, beautiful view.
颇为破旧但景观极佳
What about you?
你呢？
I live up here.
我住在这儿
That's very funny.
很有趣
Where's your family from originally?
你的家人原本从哪儿来？
They're Scots-lrish.
是苏格兰及爱尔兰裔
They emigrated to Appalachia...in the late 1700s.
1700年末期移居美国东南部
Where are you from?
你从哪儿来？
The Bay area.
三藩市湾区
Your folks there?
家人在那儿？
My mother died a long time ago, and my father...
母亲很久前死了，我父亲…
...I don't know where he is.
我不知他在哪儿
Got a brother somewhere.
我有个兄弟
You have a tight family. I can tell.
你的家人关系很紧密吧？
Right?
是吗？
You're right.
你说的对
City of lights...
灯火通明的城市
In Fiji, they have these...
在菲济，有一种…
...iridescent algae that come out once a year in the water.
会发光的海藻每年浮出水面一次
That's what it looks like out there.
这城市的灯正是如此
You been there?
你到过菲济？
No, I'm going there some day.
没有，我终有一天会去
You travel a lot?
你常旅游？
Yeah.
是的
Travelling makes you lonely?
旅游使你寂寞？
I'm alone. I am not...
我一个，可我并不…
...lonely.
寂寞
You?
你呢？
Real lonely.
很寂寞
Albert!
亚拔！
Shit!
糟了！
What you doing here? You crazy? This ain't Disneyland.
你为何来这儿？你疯了吗？
You were supposed to get back to me.
你该覆我电话的
Where the fuck you been?
你去了哪儿？
I couldn't break free.
我无法脱身
Let's violate his ass right now.
我们侵犯他的民权吧
I do for you...
我帮忙你…
...you don't do for me, is that it?
你却不帮我，是这样吗？
Listen, man. I swear, I was out all night. I'm hidden like a Flamingo matador.
我整晚外出，为你刺探消息
That's got nothing to do with me.
此事和我无关
I'm cutting it smooth. I'm generating leads and shit for you. I'm a dancer.
我顺利为你找到线索，我很棒
You bullshit.
你胡说
I paged your ass all day. I hate fucking paging.
我传呼你一整天，我讨厌这样做
You're a speed freak, jacking methamphetamine again.
你又再是瘾君子？注射毒品？
Where's your empathy? It's a substance abuse problem.
我有滥用药物的问题，心领吧？
Empathy was yesterday. Today you're wasting my motherfucking time.
我昨天对你心领你今天花我时间
You fall in love?
你爱上了？
Did you fall in love...
你是否恋爱…
...and went off somewhere?
和到别处去？
Tell me that, I'll settle for it.
我会接受这解释
Give me all you got!
把消息告诉我！
I swear, my brother Richard's going to talk to you.
我发誓我哥哥里察会跟你说
I heard Richard?
你是说里察吗？
He's going to talk to you.
他会和你说的
He's gonna meet you tonight.
他今晚会见你
He's not here, is he?
他在这儿？
No, he'll meet you tonight.
不，他会见你
What happened to now?
现在不行吗？
I implored him because I knew you was coming this a.m.
我恳求他因我知你今早会到来
Bullshit.
胡说
I swear. He said no...
我发誓，他不肯的…
...'cause he in PhoeniX.
因他去凤凰城
"By the time I get to PhoeniX
我到了凤凰城后…
"He'll be rising
他会起程…
"He'll probably leave a note
可能留下字条…
"Right on the door"
帖在门上
Tonight's the best I can do for you.
我只能令他今晚见你
He'll meet you at BJ's on Alvarado.
今晚在艾华瓦度街BJ夜总会
At 2:00 a.m.
凌晨二时
Be there.
你去吧
You be there too.
你亦要到
I can't be there, man. I got things to do.
不行，我有事要办
I got things to do, I got places to be.
我有事办，要到别处
Be there.
你要去
Don't waste my motherfucking time!
你别浪费我时间
What is it?
是什么买卖？
It's a bank.
是银行
It depos cash on Thursday for distribution to all the other branches...
星期四会存钱以便分发各分行…
...to cover Friday payroll checks.
应付星期五支付薪金的支票
So on Thursdays, the command branch has got a full whack.
总行夹万内星期四总放满现钞
On the prowl or strong?
在途中下手还是劫银行？
Through the door.
由正门进入
How many guys?
有多少人？
About four, or three, plus a driver. You walk in, knock 'em over, walk out.
连司机四人，走进银行得手便走
You want $100,000 in advance against a ten-percent cut for that?
你要先拿十万事成后分一成？
Sounds like a cowboy score.
听似是西部牛仔劫银行
They hit the hold-up alarms, I gotta get out before the cops show.
他们按动警钟我得在之前离去
They hit three hold-up alarm systems.
他们可按动三个遇劫警钟
Two Telco and a cellular.
两个一般警钟和一个蜂窝式的…
But the signals aren't going anywhere because...
但讯号无法传送出去，因为…
...the night before...
之前一晚…
...you cut in...
你潜进银行…
...and trick out the alarm system computer...
破坏警报系统的电脑…
...to turn itself...
使电脑…
...and the video recorders off...
及录影装置…
...20 minutes before you enter.
在你下手前20分钟关掉
Architectural, electrical plans?
你有建筑及电子蓝图？
I got that.
我有
I got the boards already built. They go into the CPU.
我建造电脑板，直驳中央处理器
What's the estimate?
估计可有多少钱？
12.1, 12.2 million.
1210万到1220万
You're on.
我会参加
Congratulations.
恭喜
Let me give you a little idea of where my estimates come from.
我告诉你如何估计会有这笔钱
Nobody knew the merch was yours.
没人知道货是你的
My way, you get 100 percent from the insurance company...take the bonds back from us...
我让你得保险全数赔偿以六成价
...at 60 cents on the dollar and make yourself another 40 percent.
把债券回购你可多赚四成
The operation doesn't skip a beat. We all make out.
行动全无损失我们均可赚大钱
Sure, you got a deal.
我同意
Good, because there's no percentage if everyone gets upset.
好，若大家不喜欢便没得益
You have your man call me and we'll set the meet.
要你的人给我电话，安排会面
Yeah, okay.
好的
Nice talking to you.
高兴和你通电话
You gonna deal with these guys?
你和他们交易？
Word's on the street it's okay to steal my stuff.
江湖上可接受我偷自己的东西吗
I'm going to kill these sons of bitches.
我会杀了这班浑蛋
Have Harry bring me the spreadsheets for Canary Island's Offshore.
命哈利给我加那利群岛的试算纸
That's not really an estimate. Those are eXact figures.
这些不是估计，是实在数字
I have a printout of the bank's cash flow for the past two months.
我印出银行过去两月的现金帐
How'd you get this information?
资料怎得来的？
Just comes to you.
送上门的
This stuff just flies through the air.
资料府拾皆是
It's just beamed out all over the place. You just have to grab it.
到处传送，只需加以掌握便行
I know how to grab it.
我懂得掌握
Okay, here we go.
这是我们要的
13.9 million.
1390万
- I bought it. - Good.
我同意了
What did I tell you?
我没说错吧
Here.
拿着
We're on. Call Van Zant, collect the money.
同意了，联络宏山和收钱吧
How is he?
他怎样？
He's a businessman.
他是生意人
Chris is at my place.
基斯在我家中
What's wrong?
怎么了？
Husband and wife stuff.
夫妻的争吵
I'll let him sleep it off.
我让他睡醒再算
What happened to you?
你怎么了？
When will you get some furniture?
你何时买家具？
When I get around to it.
我有时间便买
Charlene's gonna leave me.
莎莲要离开我
Why?
为什么？
Not enough steaks in the freezer.
我无好好供养她
With everything we've been doing?
我们做买卖还不够钱？
Vegas and the Super Bowl cleaned me out.
赌场及赌球赛使我身无分文
When you gonna get an old lady?
你何时会结婚？
When I get around to it.
有时间再算
You got something else on the side?
你有外遇吗？
Nothing regular.
没固定的
She got something else on the side?
她有外遇吗？
You sure?
你肯定吗？
Yeah, I'm sure.
肯定
I don't know what you're doing.
我不知你做什么
As Jimmy said, " You want to be making moves on the street?
如占美说，你想当罪犯吗？
"Have no attachments. Allow nothing to be in your life...
要无牵挂，生活中不能有…
"...that you can't walk out on in 30 seconds if you spot the heat around the corner."
任何牵挂，风声紧时可一走了之
Remember that?
记得吗？
For me, the sun rises and sets with her, man.
她是我一生中最重要的
We take delivery of cash from Van Zant...
我们从宏山那儿拿到钱…
...then I drop a deposit on Kelso for this bank.
然后为劫银行的事存钱给祈素
Bank? What bank?
什么银行？
What about the platinum thing? It's ready to fall.
这白金的事如何？快成事了
That goes too. Then the bank.
那亦会进行，然后再劫银行
Want some breakfast?
要吃早餐吗？
Are you okay?
你没事吧？
Yeah, sugar.
没事
For real.
是真的
I'll do good.
我会好好的做
I'll see you later.
再见
You Solenko?
你是索伦戈？
Don Breedan.
当毕顿
Grierson, my parole officer, told me to come by here, see if you had a job for me.
假释官告诉我你会有工作给我
You're familiar with this kind of operation?
你对工作稔熟吗？
I'm a great grill man.
我烧烤很出色的
Good. Good for you.
好
You'll mop the toilets, hit the dishwasher, bus tables and empty the garbage.
你洗抹厕所，洗碗碟收拾桌子
Give me a hard time, I'll report you loaded, drunk or stealing.
你烦我我举报你藏毒酗酒或偷窃
I'll violate you back fast.
很快举报你违假释条例
Twenty-five percent of your take-home kicks back to me.
你给我薪金的25%作回佣
Rules of the game. Call Grierson, check it out. Change in the back.
是规矩，问假释官吧，后面更衣
What are you waiting for?
你还等什么？
Malibu Equity and Investments.
马莉堡股票及投资
Roger Van Zant.
罗杰宏山
Please hold.
请等一等
This is Roger Van Zant.
我是罗杰宏山
I'm supposed to get something.
我该有一些东西的
Someone will call you back from another line.
会有人给你电话
818-133-6089.
818-133-6089…
I got a package for you. There's a drive-in on Centinela. 2:30 tomorrow.
明午二时半露天影院见
Just send one man, alone.
只派一人单独前来
- Who was that guy? - Nobody.
那人是谁？
I gotta know who he is! Who is he?
我要知道他是谁
He's nobody, Neil.
他是无名小卒
He's a legit liquor salesman from Las Vegas. Alan Marciano.
是赌城合法酒类营业员马亚伦
Chris will make up.
基斯会和你和解
- It's too late! I'm sick of him! - Shut up!
太迟了！我讨厌他！
Here's the deal. You'll give Chris one last shot.After that, he fucks up,
你再给基斯一次机会若他犯错…
then I will finance setting you up myself... ...on my own, anywhere you want.
我会资助你找地方住，哪儿也可
Dominick will go with you.
多明会跟着你
And my word counts. But right now...
我言出必行的，但现在…
...you will give him the chance.
你会给他机会
Clean up, go home.
清洗一下，回家去
Clean up, go home!
清洗一下回家！
Give me your money.
交出你的钱
You'll get smoked with that shit.
你会因此而没命的
Won't be you.
杀我的不会是你
He's coming in alone. Send him through.
他一个人来
Vincent, hey, man.
云信
This is my brother, Richard. Vincent.
这是我哥哥里察，云信
It's all right.
没关系
What have you got for me?
你有何消息告诉我？
Before we even get into that, there's this crew ripping rides all along the beach.
谈正题前，沙滩附近有人偷车
Now, in the back of a trim shop...
在汽车装饰店后
...that somebody wants to pay a little visit this weekend...
若周末有人前去那儿…
...they might find two Turbos and a 911 slope.
会找到一辆名贵跑车
You looking to rid yourself of your competition?
你参加赛车吗？
I'm a good citizen.
我是个好市民
I'm Donald Duck.
我才不信
You got something to tell me?
你有事要告诉我？
Check this out, cuz.
你听着，朋友
How do I know if I tell you what you need to know...
我怎知若我说出你所想知的事…
...that you gonna do what the fuck I need to get done.
你会做我所想做的事
Hanna is straight up.
韩很可靠的
I ain't your cuz, you rat motherfucker.
杂种，我不是你的朋友
And you know because I say so...
你知道我说得出做得到…
...after I hear what the fuck you got to tell me!
但我要先听你有什么话要说
Fuck you.
操你妈
You understand?
明白吗？
I'd get killed for telling you.
我说出来会没命的
You'd get killed walking your doggie!
你溜狗时亦会没命
All right, man...
好吧
...there was a cat I was locked up with.
我和这人在狱中…
Did a couple of two, three years. He got out. I ran into him.
服刑两三年，他出狱后我碰上他
And so?
那又怎样？
He's a big fiend for action.
他是坐言起行的人
Now, if he'd have said nothing, I'd have thought nothing, but...
若他不说我便不会去想，可是…
...he goes on and on, running down to me how he ain't done nothing...
他不断的对我说他什么也没做…
...and nothing's been going on and all this bullshit.
而且也没事发生，等等
Right then and there I know...
那时我便知道…
...this cat's got something going down.
这人参与了不法行为
Pretty fucking great.
而且是大案
Albert, what's wrong with you?
亚拔，你怎么回事了？
You drag me here, waste my time like this.
你要我来这里，浪费我的时间
You saw a guy on the street who's an eX-con?
你见过坐过牢的人？
That's right.
是的
Well, I am...
那么我…
...over-fucking-whelmed.
很喜出望外
What do you want for that, a G-man badge?
你想为此拿警章吗？
You gonna make the call on them Porches?
你会查跑车的事吗？
Is he kidding me?
他是说笑吗？
I'm telling you:
我告诉你
Slick is no joke.
滑头不是说笑的，
He's double time.
他为人紧张
Say what?
你说什么？
"Slick." What does that mean?
滑头，是什么意思？
That's what he calls people: "Slick."
他常叫别人为“滑头”
Tell me about him.
把他的事告诉我
About 6 feet tall...
他约六尺高…
...lots of jailhouse tats.
有许多监狱的纹身
Got a big-ass peacock right here.
这儿刺有一头大孔雀
What's his name?
他叫什么名字？
Cheritto.
姓查
Michael Cheritto.
查米高
Thirty-three busts since 1976.
自1976年起被捕33次
Eleven for armed robbery, three convictions.
11次持械行劫，3次给定罪
Two out of a three-to-five year beef in Attica.
判刑3至5年在纽约服刑两年
Three years in Marion.
中西部服刑3年
Five years in Folsom off a knock-back to involuntary manslaughter.
因误杀罪在霍森监狱服刑5年
Jacket's two inches thick.
他的案底达两英寸厚
Who do I have there now?
现在还有谁有听？
- Drucker and me. And Schwartz. - Tell SIS...
泽加、我和舒华兹
...I want full surveillance. That's 24 hours. Round the clock, day and night.
我要24小时监视他
We never close. Open every day.
不断监视跟踪他
Bug the car, the house, the work.
监听他的汽车和房子
When he moves or sits, like in a restaurant......I want pictures of who he moves and sits with.
一举一动和谁人一起也拍照
Then run makes on them. They got jackets, trail them.
调查他们，若有案底便跟踪他们
I want it up and running by tomorrow night.
我要明天便执行
Put your hands where I can see them.
把手放在我看到的地方
I tell you what to do.I tell you how to do it.
我会告诉你做什么及怎样去做
Now, with your right hand only, your right hand only...
现在，只用你的右手只准右手…
...take the package and throw it in here.
把包裹拿出来，扔过来
Behind you.On the right.
你右面后面有人
Roger Van Zant.
罗杰宏山
Who's this?
你是谁？
You know who this is.
你知道我是谁
Yes, I do.
我知道
I sent a guy to deliver the package.
我派人送包裹
He didn't call. Is everything okay?
他没来电话，一切妥当吧
I tell you what, forget the money.
我告诉你，忘记那笔钱
What?
什么？
Forget the money.
忘记那笔钱
It's a lot of money. What are you doing? What do you mean, "forget the money"?
数目不少，你做什么？
What am I doing? I'm talking to an empty telephone.
我对着话筒自说自话
I don't understand.
我不明白
'Cause there is a dead man on the other end of this line.
因为电话的另一端是个死人
Do you like it?
你喜欢吗？
Look at my ring.
看我的戒指
Did you know?
你知道的？
You are insane.
你疯了
Do you like it?
喜欢吗？
- It's beautiful. - It's good.
很漂亮
Don't ask him where he got it.
别问他哪儿得来的
What do you want to be when you grow up?
你长大后想做什么？
I don't know.
我不知道
Just like me.
像我一样
I don't know either.
我亦不知道
Hello?
你好
It's me.
是我
I was wondering if you'd call.
我在想你是否会来电话
I've been busy.
我很忙
Can I see you?
我可见你吗？
I was afraid that was just...
我害怕那只是…
...the one night.
一夜情
Not for me, it wasn't.
对我来说不是
Yeah, me neither.
我也不是
Can I fall by?
我可来吗？
Yeah.
可以
I'll see you in a little bit.
一会儿见
All right.
好的
Goddamn convention.
可恶的会议
- Which one's Slick? - The wide one.
哪一个是滑头？ 魁悟的那个
We got two transmitters.
有两个监视器
One's in the wheel well, backup's in the firewall.
分别在防火板及轮内
Here we are.
是我们的车
Did you say good night to Neil?
跟尼尔道别了吗？
The blond is Chris Shiherlis.
金发的是施基斯
SIS has got a revolving tail and hung a wire on the house phone.
特别调查姐派人跟他偷听电话
Cheritto's cruised the precious-metals depository three times.
查把车三次驶过贵重金属库
Platinum, silver, and some bullion.
白金、银和一些金条
Sammy and I think that's going to be their neXt score.
森美和我认为是他们下一目标
Who's the loner?
那独行者是谁？
First time we're seeing him.
我们第一次见他
We're not on him yet.
还没开始跟踪他
Get on it.
立即开始吧
When these guys walk out the door of whatever score they're gonna take neXt...
他们下次做案得手走出大门时…
...they're gonna have the surprise of a lifetime.
定会大感惊愕
Baby, time to go.
我要走了
Showed you a good time, didn't I?
我令你很开心吧
You fly.
你很棒
You cool.
你不错
You're lying to me. I can always tell when people lie to me.
你骗我，我看得出别人骗我
I ain't lying.
我没说谎
You a hot dog.
你很勇猛
A regular rodeo rider.
是出色的骑士
And this was the monster fuck of my young life.
是我试过最精彩的性行为
Now, I got to get my ass street-side, sugar.
我现在得回到街上去
You don't have a truth-telling style.
你没有老实的作风
What are you talking about?
你说什么？
You don't know what this is.
你不知道是什么回事？
The Grim Reaper's visiting with you.
是死神来探望你
Where have you been?
你去了哪儿？
SHU at Pelican Bay.
塘鹅弯的特别收容所
And Folsom, B-wing.
以及霍森监狱B座
I am a cowboy...
我是一个…
...looking for anything heavy.
想做大买卖的人
Billy said to come see you.
比利说来找你
That is why I am here.
因此我到来
Why don't you call this guy?
你给这人电话吧
This guy's always putting guys on.
他经常招人入伙
Thank you.
谢谢
You're perfect for each other.
你们天生一对
I knew a guy in grade school.
我念小学时认识一人
His name was Raoul... whatever.
他叫罗尔…什么的
You could take his fingers and fold them over each other.
他可把手指彼此屈折起来
He'd turn his eyelids inside out...
他可把眼睑向外翻…
I can't keep my hands off you. That's the truth.
我禁不住对你上下其手，是真的
That's what's so wonderful about you in that...
你吸引的地方在于你那…
...bestial sort of way.
兽性的方式
Woman.
女人
This better be earth-shattering.
这最好是轰动的大事
This is to Raoul.
为罗尔干杯
Yeah, Vincent Hanna.
我是韩云信
Here's how we found her.
发现她时是这样的
How old?
她有多大？
16, 17. Been here about siX hours.
十六七岁，在此约六小时
How'd she die?
她怎么死的？
Beat her head in, same as the others. Cerebral hematoma.
头部给重击，大脑血肿
Who's that?
那是谁？
Mother and siblings.
死者母亲及兄弟
- Why are they here? - It's fucked up.
他们为何到来？
Somebody inside knew the girl and called the family.
酒店内有人认识死者通知家人
Let's go.
让我看看
Nice.
不错
My intuition says the check on the semen will show it's the same guy...
直觉告诉我化验精液是同一人…
...so it's a series and ending up in your court.
是连环谋杀案，要由你着手调查
Sheriff's getting anywhere?
警长有头绪吗？
Not yet.
还没有
Get off of me!
放开我！
Oh, my God!
天啊！
Where is she?
她在哪儿？
Easy, easy, easy.
冷静！
Please, come on.
别这样
It's okay. It's okay.
没事的
Where is my baby? Where is she?
我的女儿呢？
I need to know what happened.
我要知是什么回事
I guess the earth shattered.
我猜是很轰动吧
So why didn't you let Bosko take you home?
你为何不让博高送你回家？
I didn't want to ruin their night too.
我不想扫他们的兴
What was it?
有什么事？
You don't want to know.
你不想知道的
I'd like to know what's behind that grim look on your face.
我想知道你为何扳起脸孔
I don't do that. You know it. Let's go.
我不能透露，你是知道的
You never told me I'd be eXcluded.
你从没告诉我我会摒诸事外
I told you when we hooked up...
我告诉你我们在一起时…
...that you were gonna have to share me...
你要和我分享…
...with all the bad people and all the ugly events on this planet.
世上所有的丑行及丑恶的人
And I bought into that sharing...
我同意接受分享…
...because I love you.
因为我爱你
I love you fat, bald, money, no money, driving a bus.
你发胖、秃头、没钱我仍爱你，开巴士
I don't care.
我不在乎
But you have got to be present like a normal guy.
但你定要存在
That's sharing. This is not sharing, this is leftovers.
那是分享，这不是分享是残余的
What I should do is come home and say:
我该回家和我该说：
"Hi, honey, guess what? I walked into this house today...
你知道吗？我今天走进一房子…
"...where this junkie asshole just fried his baby in a microwave...
这瘾君子用微波炉煮熟了孩子…
"...because he was crying too loud, so let me share that with you.
因他哭的太吵闹，我和你分享吧
"Come on, let's share that and in sharing it...
让我们分享此事，而在分享时…
"...we'll somehow cathartically dispel all that heinous shit."
我们会宣泄一切可怕的事件
Right?
对吗？
Wrong.
错
You know why?
你知道是何解？
'Cause you prefer the normal routine.
你喜欢正常的做法
We fuck and you don't speak.
我们做爱，你不说话
'Cause I got to hold onto my angst.
我得保持我的痛苦
I preserve it...
我保存它…
...because I need it. It keeps me sharp, on the edge.
因为我需要藉此提高警觉
Where I gotta be.
我要这样做
You don't live with me.
你不是和我同住
You live among the remains of dead people.
你和死者的残骸同住
You sift through the detritus.You read the terrain.
你筛选碎片 在地势找线索
You search for signs of passing...
你找寻死亡的迹象…
...for the scent of your prey...
找猎物的气味…
...and then you hunt them down.
然后追捕他们
That's the only thing you're committed to.
这是你唯一投入的事
The rest is the mess you leave as you pass through.
其余的是你留下的烂摊子
What I don't understand is why I can't cut loose of you.
我不明白为何不能离开你
Let's go, baby.
走吧
I met the manager.
我见过经理
Is that the boss?
那是老板吗？
I did time for what that motherfucker does every day.
我为他每天所做的事而坐牢
Can you just handle it till we find you something new?
你可忍受直至找到新工作吗？
Can you do that?
你可以吗？
Ain't a hard time been invented that I cannot handle.
更难忍受的我亦捱过
What you're hanging with me for?
你为何和我一起
Because I'm proud of you.
因为你令我感骄傲
You're proud of me?
你以我为荣？
Why the hell are you proud of me?
为什么？
Come on home.
回家吧
What were you doing there?
你在做什么？
I was skiing.
我滑雪
I was trying to ski.
我想滑雪
That's what people do there. You go skiing...
那儿的人会这样做，去滑雪…
...and you meet people.
可结识别人
You try to have a good time.
你想开心一下
- Did you have a good time? - No.
你开心吗？
Why not?
为什么？
I'm not good at meeting people.
我不擅交际
You met me.
你认识了我
That happened without my thinking about it.
我没加细想事情便发生了
Which is why I probably...
可能是因为这样…
No, it's because you are fine.
不，是因为你是好的女子
Take off with me for a while.
和我到外地去
Where?
去哪？
New Zealand.
新西兰
When?
何时？
I have to go separate. You can meet me there.
我不能和你去，你可会合我
But my job...
但我的工作
I got money. You don't need money.
我有钱，你不用工作
You could set up a studio and work there.
你可在那儿开设计公司
I don't know.
我不知道
What's there to know?
还要知道什么？
Are you married?
你结了婚没有？
What?
什么？
The last thing I am is married.
我才没有结婚
I'm a needle starting at zero going the other way.
我的生活正在走下坡
Then, all of a sudden...
可是，突然…
...someone like you comes along.
出现了你这样的人
You don't know me.
你不了解我
I know enough.
我已了解
Come with me.
跟我走
What's wrong?
有何不妥？
Nothing's wrong. Everything's right. Will you go?
没什么，一切妥当，你会去吗？
Yeah.
会
Good.
好
Hi, sweetie.
亲爱的
You forget your mom was picking you up?
你忘记妈妈会接你吗？
No.
不是
So, what's going on?
怎么回事？
I felt like being alone.
我想独自一人
Come on, I'll drive you home.
我送你回家
What's happening?
有何动静？
Sir.
长官
Captain Jackson wants to know what's going on.
警长想知道有何动静
Nothing's going on. Stay off the air.
没动静，不要用无线电
Technique.
好技术
Open Sesame. Right there.
芝麻开门
There he is.
就是他
We walk!
我们走吧
I'm there.
我快完事了
He's heard it.
他听到了
Heads up.
他们来了
- One's coming out. - Hold it, Captain.
等一等
Vincent, he's not carrying anything.
他没带走任何东西
I see.
我看见
- Here we go. - Not till my boss says so.
行动
Both of them are not carrying anything.
由我上司批准，他们没拿东西
- Let them go. - What do you mean?
让他们走
We can take them on!
我们可拘捕他们
On what?
控以何罪？
They didn't steal anything.
他们没偷东西
It gets knocked back to a misdemeanor, they do siX months and they're out.
行为不检他们坐牢半年便出狱
No fucking way.
不行
I'm not taking the heat from my boss. They are not walking.
我不会接受批评，他们不能走
That's eXactly what they'll do. They'll walk. This is my operation.
他们会走，今次行动由我指挥
I have tactical command that supersedes your rank.
我的战略指挥凌驾你的职级
They will walk away and you will let them. Fuck!
他们会离去，你会让他们走
Back to work.
继续工作
LAPD, the G, what? Where the fuck did this heat come from?
罗省警方？密探？警方从何来？
Maybe it's the score they were onto. The place, not us.
他们或知那儿被劫不知是我们
Because it's been hit a couple of times.
因为那儿以前曾遇劫
Assume they got our phones, our houses. Assume they got us right here, right now...
假设他们知道我们的电话住所
...as we sit. Everything. Assume it all.
假设一切
How are we gonna buy the bank package?
我们如何付劫银行的上期？
I'll front that.
我先垫付吧
What if Van Zant has 750?
宏山呢？
With the heat we got, you want to play World War II on the streets with Van Zant?
警方追查我们你想和他开战吗？
No, I want my 750.
不，我想拿75万
I got more motivation to whack Van Zant than either of you. He is a fucking luXury.
我比你更想杀了宏山
Our problem is to take the bank, or split right now.
问题是我们劫银行还是离去
Do not go home, do not pack, nothing.
不要回家收拾东西
Thirty seconds flat from now, we are gone on our separate ways. That's it.
30秒后我们会各走各路
The bank is worth the risk.
值得冒险劫银行
I need it, brother.
我需要钱
We should stay and take it down. That's where I come out.
我认为我们该留下来劫银行
I roll with you, Neil. Whatever.
你做什么我亦跟随
- Whatever. - Not on this one.
但今次不行
On this one, you're on your own.
你要自行决定
You figure this is the best thing to do?
这是最好的做法吗？
This is the best thing to do?
是最好的做法吗？
I've got plans, I'm going away after, so the reward is worth the stretch.
事后我有打算值得为这笔钱坐牢
But Elaine takes good care of you. You got plenty put away.
但绮玲很照顾你，你有许多钱
You got T-bonds, real estate.
你有物业，若我是你…
If I were you, I would be smart and cut loose of this.
便不参与今次行动
For me...
对我来说…
...the action is the juice.
行动使生活更刺激
I'm in.
我参加
Yeah, sure.
我会
Let's go.
动手吧
Fuck them, let's do it.
去他们的，行动吧
Let's go. We got a lot of work to do.
我们有许多事要做
Tim, I gotta call you back.
添，我给你电话吧
- Can I help you? - Are you Alan Marciano?
你是马亚伦吗？
Who the fuck are you?
你是谁？
Who am I?
我是谁？
Lieutenant Vincent Hanna, LAPD.
罗省警局的韩云信探长
LA? This is Las Vegas. You don't even have jurisdiction here.
这儿是赌场不是你权力范围
Do you know who the fuck you're pushing around? I know people here.
你知在惹恼谁吗？我认识人
Las Vegas PD takes you into custody.
我可要赌城警方拘押你
You are eXtradited to Newark on a warrant for smuggling cigarettes...
你会因从北卡罗来纳走私香烟…
...up from North Carolina three years ago...
而给引渡回纽华克…
...or you go to work for us.
或是你可和我们合作
Cut and dried.
简单明快
That is it.
就是这样
Shit.
操
Charlene Shiherlis.
施莎莲
Who?
谁？
What are you, a fucking owl?
你是猫头鹰吗？
The lady you been talking dirty to on the telephone every day last week.
和你在电话中淫声浪语的女子
You can't tie me to her.
你不能把她和我扯上了
Who needs to? Your ass is on a plane back to New Jersey, jackoff.
你肯定会回去新泽西的，笨蛋
Why did I get miXed up with her?
我为何会勾搭上她？
Because she got a great ass!
因为她的屁股动人
And you got your head all the way up it.
你不知自己在做什么
Jesus.
天啊
Ferocious, aren't I?
我很凶，是吗？
When I think of asses...
当我想起屁股…
...a woman's ass...
女人的屁股…
...something comes out of me.
便想起一些东西
So?
那么？
So, no big thing.
不要你说太多
All I want...
我只想…
...is her husband and his whole fucking crew.
知她丈夫和他那伙人
You'll work with Sgt. Drucker.
你会和泽加合作
San Clemente Road and Hermosa...
圣金文路和赫摩撒街
...that's where we cut through the fence. That's the access.
我们在那儿穿过栏栅
Right.
对
The security systems around here are a joke.
保安系统不堪一击
St. Vincent Thomas Bridge, that's escape route number one.
逃走路线一是圣云逊汤玛士桥
Number two:
路线二…
Over here. Anaheim to the 110.
是安纳咸公路往110公路
Good.
好
You got it?
明白吗？
Good. Let's go.
好的，走吧
They were looking back...
他们回头望向…
...in this direction.
这方向
A container facility?
货柜设施？
What? Cartage theft?
什么？
Too visible. Too lowball for them.
太明显了 对他们来说得益太少了
There's an oil refinery and a scrap yard.
有炼油厂、废车场
Refinery pays by check.
炼油厂发薪用支票
No cash around.
没有现金
Same for the scrap yard.
废车场亦一样
Stealing hubcaps?
偷车轮盖？
A refinery and a scrap yard.
炼油厂和废车场？
What the hell is going on?
是什么回事？
That's what we are trying to figure out.
我们正想知道
We thought we had it.
我们以为已知道了
I got an idea...
我知道…
...on what they're looking at.
他们在看些什么
Want to know what they're looking at?
你们要知吗？
I mean, is this guy something, or is he something?
这人真了不起，他真行
This crew is good.
这伙人很棒
You want to know?
你们想知吗？
What?
是什么？
Us.
是我们
The LAPD.
罗省警局
The police department.
是警局
We just got made.
我们给人认出了
Yeah!
耶
Okay!
好吧
Okay, motherfucker!
好吧，杂种
Kelso come through?
祈素交出了吗？
Yeah, you can build a bank with these.
交出了，蓝图很详尽
Name is Hanna.
那人姓韩
First name, Vincent.
名云信
I smeared this sergeant five yards.
我用五百元贿赂这警员
Hanna's all over you.
韩监视你一举一动
He's on all the work cars. Michael's house. Shiherlis's.
监视所有的车、米高及施的家
Not yours. They've been losing you at night.
没监视你，不知你晚上在哪儿
He's a hot dog.
他很积极
Graduate school. Marine Corps.
他毕业后加以陆战队
Lieutenant in Robbery-Homicide.
是劫案及凶杀组探长
He's taken down some heavy crews. He blew away Frankie in Chicago.
拘捕不少人在芝加哥杀了法兰
He was a fucking maniac.
法兰是个狂人
He was working narcotics before that.
他之前在毒品科工作
Divorced twice. Current wife's Justine.
离婚两次，目前的太太叫彩钿
He's why the eXtra heat.
是他鼓动严密监视的
The vice sergeant...
罪案科警官…
...says Hanna likes you...
说韩喜欢你…
...thinks you're some kind of star. You do this sharp, that sharp.
认为你是明星，行事很有技巧
Look how sharp this guy is to figure that.
他能想到这样看他有多聪明
Funny as a heart attack.
他像心脏病般好笑
Three marriages? Do you think that means he likes staying home?
三次结婚？你认为他喜欢在家？
Means he's one of those guys out there...
他是那种…
...prowling around all night, dedicated.
整晚工作的人，很投入
With him and this much heat, you should pass.
有他和警方监视取消劫银行吧
It's worth the stretch.
值得冒险一试
This guy can hit or miss.
这人可抓到我或是失手
You can't miss once.
你不能出错
You sure?
你肯定吗？
I am sure.
肯定
Let's go to the garage.
我们去车房吧
Where are we going?
我们去哪里？
Where are you going?
你去哪里？
Out.
外出
What are they on?
他们用什么频道？
TAC 9.
九号战术频道
They're northbound out LAX on the 405.
他们在405公路
We got four ground units.
往机场方向北走
This is Vincent Hanna in Air 18.
我是18号机的韩云信
Who have I got?
谁和我合作？
This is JJ. I'm in Air 40.
我是40号机的JJ
Richard Glover's with me.
高里察和我一起
It's on the 105 eastbound...
车在105公路…
...approaching the 110.
东行接近110公路
Revolving tail?
交替追踪？
I got two units in front, three behind.
前有两辆车，三辆在他后面
Have one of them pick me up at the Vermont on-ramp.
要其中一辆在维蒙街接我
Let's go.
走吧
Am I 100 yards, or what? Am I close or far, or what?
我离他百码吗？太近还是太远？
Three hundred yards, center lane.
离他300码，在中央行车线
How're you doing?
你好吗？
What do you say I buy you a cup of coffee?
我请你喝咖啡如何？
Yeah, sure. Let's go.
好的，走吧
Follow me.
跟我走
Seven years in Folsom.
你在霍森监狱七年
In the hole for three.
单独囚禁三年
McNeil before that.
之前在麦尼尔监狱
McNeil as tough as they say?
那儿是一如所说的那么凶残吗？
You looking to become a penologist?
你是监狱学者吗？
You looking to go back?
你想再坐牢？
I chased down some crews. Guys just looking to fuck up, get busted back.
我追捕想犯错被捕的人拘捕他们
That you?
那人是你吗？
You must've worked some dipshit crews.
你拘捕的定是饭桶了
I worked all kinds.
我拘捕各式各样的人
You see me doing liquor store holdup with a "Born to Lose" tattoo on my chest?
你幻想我身上有刺青行劫酒铺吗
I do not.
我不是
Right.
对
I am never going back.
我不会再坐牢
Then don't take down scores.
那么便别再行劫
I do what I do best.
我做擅长做的事
I take scores. You do what you do best: Try to stop guys like me.
我行劫，你做擅长的事，阻止我
You never wanted a regular type life?
你从不想过正常生活？
What is that? The barbecues and the ball games?
是怎样的？烧烤和打足球吗？
Yeah.
是的
This regular type like your life?
你的生活正常吗？
My life? No, my life...
我的生活？不，我的生活…
My life's a disaster zone.
一塌糊涂
I got a stepdaughter so fucked up...
我的继女情绪深受困扰
...because her real father is this large-type asshole.
因她的生父是个大浑蛋
I got a wife.
我有太太…
We're passing each other on the down slope of a marriage.My third.
我三次婚姻正频临破碎边缘
Because I spend all my time chasing guys like you around the block.
因我常花时间追捕你这样的人
That's my life.
那是我的生活
Guy told me one time:
有人曾对我说…
"Don't get attached to anything you can't walk out on in 30 seconds...
若你感到附近有警方监视
"...if you feel the heat around the corner."
便不能沾上任何不能脱身的事
If you're on me and you got to move when I move...
你想捉我，我行动时你亦行动…
...how do you eXpect to keep a marriage?
你如何能保持婚姻呢？
That's an interesting point.
这说法很有趣
What are you, a monk?
你是僧侣吗？
I have a woman.
我有女伴
What do you tell her?
你怎对她说？
I tell her I'm a salesman.
我是推销员
So, if you spot me coming around that corner...
那么若你见我从街角走来…
...you'll just walk out on her?
你会离开她？
Not say good-bye?
不辞而别？
That's the discipline.
那是自律
That's pretty vacant.
那很空泛
It is what it is.
正是如此
It's that, or we both better go do something else.
不这样做我们还是另找职业吧
I don't know how to do anything else.
我不懂做别的
Neither do I.
我也不懂
I don't want to either.
我不想
You know, I have this recurring dream.
我不断重复这梦境
I'm sitting at this big banquet table and...
我坐在偌大的餐宴席上…
...all the victims of all the murders I ever worked are sitting there...
我调查的凶案受害人均出席…
...and they're staring at me with these black eyeballs...
他们用黑的眼珠子瞪望我…
...because they got eight-ball hemorrhages from the head wounds.
因为他们头部中枪而出血
And there they are, these big balloon people...
这些发胀的尸体在那儿…
...because I found them two weeks after they'd been under the bed.
因他们被杀两周后才在床下发现
The neighbors reported the smell...
邻居报称有恶臭…
...and there they are...
他们均有出席…
...all just sitting there.
坐在那儿
What do they say?
他们说什么？
Nothing.
没说话
No talk?
没人说话？
They have nothing to say.
他们无话可说
We just look at each other.
我们彼此望着对方
They look at me...
他们望着我…
...and that's it. That's the dream.
就是这样，梦境是这样
I have one where I'm drowning.
我做梦自己遇溺
I gotta wake myself up and start breathing or I'll die in my sleep.
我得弄醒自己和呼吸否则会死
What's that about?
这象征什么？
Having enough time.
有足够的时间
Enough time...
足够时间…
...to do what you want to do?
做你想做的事？
That's right.
是的
You doing it now?
你现在这样做？
No, not yet.
还没有
You know, we're sitting here...
我们坐在这里…
...like a couple of regular fellas.
一如常人，
You do what you do, and I do what I gotta do.
彼此做有需要的事
Now that we've been face to face...
现在我们见过面…
...if I'm there and I gotta put you away...
若我要在案发现场杀你…
...I won't like it.
我会不喜欢
But, I tell you...
但是…
...if it's between you...
若在你和…
...and some poor bastard whose wife you're gonna turn into a widow...
给你杀死的人当中作选择…
...brother...
兄弟…
...you are going down.
没命的会是你
There's a flip side to that coin.
我有反面的看法
What if you do got me boXed in...
若你真的使我走投无路…
...and I gotta put you down?
而我要杀你呢？
Because no matter what...
因为不管如何…
...you won't get in my way.
你亦不能阻止我的
We've been face to face, yeah.
是的，我们见过面
But I will not hesitate.
但我会毫不犹疑杀你
Not for a second.
一秒也不迟疑
Maybe that'll happen.
也许会这样
Or...
或是…
...who knows?
谁晓得呢？
Maybe we'll never see each other again.
也许我们会永远不再见
They dumped us.
他们摆脱了我们
What?
什么？
What do you mean?
什么意思？
Chris slipped away.
基斯狡脱了
He doesn't talk about their scores...
他没谈及买卖的事
...so there's nothing for me to get from Marciano. I just tried.
我无从向马套取资料
- What about Cheritto? - Same.
查米高呢？ 亦一样
Transponders got put on a bus to San Clemente.
异频收发器放在公共汽车上
They dumped all our surveillance?
他们摆脱我们所有的监视？
Yes, at the same time. 9:00 p.m.
是的，同一时间，间上九时
I had coffee with McCauley half an hour ago!
我半小时前和麦尼尔喝咖啡
His car's still there. He's gone.
他的车上仍在，不见了他
Does anybody have any idea where the fuck these people are?
有谁知道他们在哪儿？
Hear from him?
他有联络吗？
Not a thing. And not hearing bothers me more. Where's this guy?
没有，这令我不安，他在哪儿？
This guy...
这人…
...we put him on.
我们雇用他
Says he knows McCauley.
他说认识麦尼尔
Who are you?
你是谁？
Waingro.
荣谷
My name's Waingro.
我叫荣谷
I've been living in this office. How well do you know him?
我等他电话，你很熟识他吗？
We took some major scores together.
我们一起做过不少大买卖
Why haven't I heard from him?
他为何没找我？
He's probably busy right now.
他可能忙着
But he's real thorough.
但他行事很彻底
He ain't going to forget about you.
他不会忘记你的
That's reassuring.
那令人很安心
I got some moves I could make here.
我可在这儿出了力
Probably be a big help to you.
可能对你会很有帮助
You recognize the grill man?
认得那烤肉的人吗？
No.
不认识
Folsom.
霍森监狱
D-block. Housed with Dobie Rush.
D座的，和杜比同一囚室
I ain't got my break yet.
我还没有小休
Cisco and Pancho didn't show.
薜哥和彭曹没上班
Haul out the garbage. Mop up the back.
扔垃圾，到餐厅后抹地
Take your break later.
稍后才休息吧
Piece of shit.
人渣
Pick up!
送出去吧
Where the hell is he?
他在哪儿？
I want to check the slot for the work car.
我查看车场看车是否仍在那儿
So did I.
我也想
Hang on.
等一等
Use the land line. Call me at 103-7206.
用普通电话 打来103-7206
Where are you?
你在哪儿？
There's cops all over me, man, like a cheap suit.
到处有警察监视我
I can't dump them.
我无法摆脱他们
They know you see them?
他们知道你看见他们
They're doing parallels.
他们平衡紧帖我
I can try to dump them again.
我可试行摆脱他们
How are we going to know if you did?
我怎知道你是否摆脱了？
You'll draw them to us.
你会引他们来找我们
Go to Ventura.Pull them out of here.
到宏杜拿去
I'm sorry. Last thing I wanted to do was let you down.
对不起，我不想让你失望的
Pick up.
送出去
Neil, man. What's up?
尼尔，你好吗？
What's up?
你好吗？
What are you doing here?
你在这儿做什么？
I'm looking for a driver who can handle scanners on the radio.
我找可应付警方追踪的司机
Right now, today.
现在便要
You remember the drill?
你还记得吗？
Yeah, sure.
记得
You cool?
你可信任吗？
You know I'm cool.
你知我可信任
One answer, yes or no. Right now.
你现在便答我，肯或不肯
Yeah, man. Fuck, yeah. You're on.
好的，去它的 我答应
Out back in five.
五分钟后到后面
What's burning?
是什么烧焦了？
What is this?
是什么事？
Where do you think you're going?
你去哪里？
Don't move! Put your hands in the air!
别动！举手！
Hands up!
举手！
Get on your knees!
跪下！
The keys!
给我钥匙
Get over there!
过去那边！
Turn around!
转身！
Put your hands behind you!
把手放在背后！
Get down!
躺下！
Stay down!
别动
- Down! - The keys! The keys!
拿锁匙来！
We want to hurt no one. We want the bank's money, not yours.
我们不想伤人只要银行的钱
Your money is insured by the government. You won't lose a dime.
你们不会损失，政府购了保险
Think of your families.
想想你的家人，
Don't risk your life. Don't be a hero.
别冒生命危险
I want you to sit on the floor, put your hands on your head. Anybody feels sick...
你们坐在地上手放头上，不舒服
...anybody got heart trouble, lean against the wall.
或心脏有事，便靠在墙上
The key.
给我锁匙
What key?
什么锁匙？
Sit down and stay down!
都别动
Sit there. Don't move. Let it bleed.
坐下，别动，让伤口淌血吧
Get down. Down, down, down.
伏下
Put your heads down!
低下头！
You guys working a case on a Neil McCauley?
你调查麦尼尔的案？
This C.I., Hugh Benny, called in about a bank.
机密线人许班尼说关于劫银行
Far East National Bank, 11:30!
早上十一时半远东国家银行！
I want a block at Figueroa and Fifth...
在第五街交界设路障…
...and I want a block northbound Flower at SiXth.
花街及第六界北行亦设路障
They're already coming out.
他们出来了
We gotta take them in the car.
要在车上捉他们
Wait till they are all in.
等他们全上车后才动手
Get clean shots. Watch your background.
要利落的杀他们，别伤及无辜
Police! Move!
警察！走开！
Move. Move. Get down.
闪开闪开
Move it. Down, down.
走开！伏下
We did it!
我们成功了！
Move!
走开！
Get down!
伏下
Get in the car!
开车！
Go! Go!
走！
Get down!
伏下
Out of the way! Get them down! Now!
紧伏在地上！快伏下！
Come here.
过来
I got you.
我抱你
Tragedy in the neighborhood today. A bank robbery spilled out into the street.
今天发生惨剧银行劫案祸延街上
Claudia Newman, live on the scene. She has the latest.
钮歌迪现时在现场作最新报导
This afternoon, a neighborhood was terrorized by a bank holdup gone wrong.
今午劫银行不遂使这儿很可怕
With the streets full of shoppers and kids, police and armed robbers...
街上满是行人，警方和劫匪…
EXcuse me, bartender.
对不起
Our top story tonight: Robbery, pursuit and, finally, death.
新闻提要：劫匪逃走终于死亡
A Los Angeles neighborhood is shaken by a bank robbery...
银行劫案震动洛杉矶地区…
...that ended in homicide and terror.
最后以凶杀及恐惧告终
Michael Cheritto...
查米高…
...one of four men involved in the foiled robbery, died at the scene.
是四名劫匪之一，在现场死去
Also fatally wounded: ...another suspect, Donald Breedan,
另一受重伤的疑匪，当毕顿…
who died of gunshot wounds...
死于枪伤…
...during the extensive gunfire between police and suspects.
当时警方和疑匪正激烈驳火
All right, hold him.
好了，按着他
It's all right.
没事的
So?
怎样？
He's got blood loss and shock.
他失血和受惊
I'll give you quarter-grain bottles of morphine for the pain.
我给你最少量的吗啡止痛
Bottom line?
告诉我吧
It's mostly tissue damage, which is good.
主要是组织受损，那是好事
His clavicle's fractured. Can you rest?
他的锁骨折断，可让他休息吗？
SiX, seven hours.
6、7小时
- That's it? - That's it.
不能多留？
Take off your shirt.
脱下衬衣
What?
什么、
My daughter gave it to me.
这是女儿给我的
I don't give a shit. Take it off.
我不管，脱下来
Listen to me.
听着
Nate's going to pick you up. He's going to take you to his place.
奈德会接你，送你到他家中
Where's Charlene?
莎莲呢？
We gotta go. We're on the 6 o'clock news. We gotta get out of here.
新闻播银行的事，我们要离去
I'm not going without her.
没有她我不走
Think about that.
你考虑一下
I will meet you at Nate's.
在奈德那儿见
Where are you going?
你去哪儿？
To find out if our out got spilled along with every other damn thing.
查探逃走路线是否给泄露了
Who did it?
是谁告密的？
Who wasn't there?
有谁没参加？
Trejo.
齐祖
See you at Nate's.
在奈德家见
You still want me?
你仍想要我吗？
You come down here right now and you get me. Dominick and me.
你来这里接我和多明吧
Okay, baby.
好的，宝贝
I'll be there in two hours.
我两小时后到
All right.
好吧
Goddamn you, Chris.
你该死，基斯
Goddamn you.
你该死
You're on a plane to Los Angeles.
你坐飞机往罗省
Right.
是的
Why did you do it? What happened?
你为何这样做？怎么回事？
- They made me. - Who?
他们迫我
Where's Anna?
安娜呢？
She's dead.
她死了
So is Michael and Breedan, the guy who stood in for you.
米高和代替你的毕顿亦死了
Who did it?
谁迫你的？
They had Anna, man.
他们威胁安娜
Who?
是谁？
Waingro.
荣谷
On his own?
他一个人？
- For someone. - Who?
替人卖命
The other he worked for.
他替别人工作…
Van Zant.
宏山
Van Zant?
宏山？
Are you sure?
你肯定吗？
Van Zant.
宏山
Did you tell them how we're getting out?
你有说出我们怎样逃走吗？
I don't think so.
我认为没有
Come on.
说吧
I don't remember.
我不记得
I'll call a medic.
我通知救护员
I'm not going to make it.
我无法活下去的
I can't feel a bloody thing.
我全无感觉
My Anna's gone.
我的安娜死了
She's gone.
她死了
Don't leave me like this.
别这样扔下我
Please, homes.
求求你，朋友
You on a cellular? Use a hard line.
你用无线电话吗？用普通电话
It's a new one.
这是新的电话
The guy lives on Hillside Terrace, Encino.
他住在安仙奴区山景台
10725.
10725号
Chris?
基斯呢？
He's with me, my place.
他和我一起在我家中
NeXt, Waingro, okay?
跟着查出荣谷在哪儿
You got the time?
你有时间吗？
I'll make time.
我会抽空的
And I need a new out.
我要新的逃走路线
Is it blown?
已给知悉了？
How can I trust it?
我怎能信任呢？
You got it.
好的
Stay healthy.
保住性命
Charlene Shiherlis.
莎莲
Drucker's got a safe house in Venice to stash her in.
泽加在威尼斯区有地方收藏她
Neil's transportation.
尼尔的逃走方法
Get on the phone. Somewhere, someone's trying to put it together for him.
正有人替他安排一切
You don't believe he already had a plan?
你不是认为他已有计划吧？
Sure. Now he needs another.
他需要另一个计划
Would you trust yours after this afternoon?
今天之后你还相信逃走计划吗？
This rat motherfucker, where did we get him?
这告密的人，哪儿找到他的？
He's a C.I. For a burglary cop. Called in the tip on the bank.
他是机密线人通报劫银行线索
On Neil McCauley.
谈麦尼尔吧
How much time we got?
还有多少时间？
Eight, ten hours for him to set up a new out. After that, he's gone, bye-bye.
他有8至10小时安排新逃走路线
You ratted McCauley to us! How'd you know?
你向我们告发麦！你怎知道？
Who told you?
谁告诉你的？
Who told you, rat motherfucker?
是谁告诉你的？
Who?
是谁？
Waingro, where is he?
荣谷在哪儿？
Where?
在哪儿？
How would I know?
我怎知道？
Well......what do we have here?
这儿有些什么？
This pretty?
这儿漂亮吗？
You piece of shit.
你这小人
Told me you wanted out from under. You're scared, right?
你告诉我想脱离目前困境
You want out? This is out.
你想脱身吗？这是出路
- Yeah, what's your end?
你有何得益？
- I don't need no stupid broad.
我不需要笨女人
How'd I get into this?
我怎会牵涉此事的？
Easy.
别冲动
You heard me. She had a rough ride.
你听到的，她生活坎坷
FiX her a drink.Look in the cabinet above the sink.
给她喝杯酒，到橱柜看看
Fuck her.
去她的
You better get in there and stay in there.
你最好进去和不要出来
Lookie here.
听着
My name is Sgt. Drucker, LAPD Homicide.
我是泽加，
You want to put Dominick in the bedroom?
要送多明进睡房吗？
He stays with me.
他和我一起
So, what now?
现在怎办？
He's right.
他说的对
You want out? This is out.
你想脱身？这是出路
You believe you have to betray Chris?
你认为你要出卖基斯？
No shit.
正是
That's right. You would have to.
对，你要会这样做
See, if you don't betray Chris, you victimize Dominick.
若不出卖基斯多明会是受害人
'Cause he becomes an orphan when you go to prison as an accessory...
你入狱时他会是孤儿
...'cause you got no parents to take him. So he ends up raised in foster homes...
你没父母照顾他他会送收养所…
...juvenile facilities.
青少年中心
Then he steals a car.
之后他会偷车
Then he winds up in gladiator academies like Chino and Tracy.
然后入狱学会做真正的罪犯
Fucked for life.
毁了一生
You know what happens, because you've been there.
你是过来人，知道会有何下场
Dominick didn't get a chance yet to choose his life. But Chris did.
多明没机会选择生活但基斯有
If you give up Chris, you get off clean.
若供出基斯，你会没有案底
You can do it...
你可以的…
...for your kid, so you can raise him.
为孩子而这样做你可抚养他
What else are you selling?
你还有什么条件？
All kinds of shit.
各种的东西
But I don't have to sell this, you know it. This kind of shit here sells itself.
但我不用说服你因为我是对的
Here's an update.
最新消息
Drucker's on Line 2.
泽加在二线
Hold on for a second.
等一等
Drucker's on the other line.
泽加在另一电话线
Conference him in.
三人通话吧
Go ahead.
说吧
Vincent, it's me.
云信，是我
One answer. What's it going to be?
你的答覆是怎样？
We're set here. She'll make the call.
我们准备好，她会打电话
That's good. Here's the deal.
好的，情况是这样
Hugh Benny has reformed his wayward life...
许班尼已改过自新…
...and become a born-again good citizen.
成为洗心革面的好市民
Apparently, Neil got sold out to us by this cowboy named Waingro.
叫荣谷的人向我们出卖尼尔
Waingro used to be a part of Neil's crew, then went to work for a money launderer.
荣谷曾是他手下后替洗钱人工作
Van Zant.
他叫宏山
Units are at Van Zant's house as we speak...
现时正派人住宏山家中…
...because he got shot dead earlier tonight.
因为他今晚较早前被杀
If Neil goes after anybody else, it's going to be Waingro.
尼尔要对付的人会是荣谷
Waingro just got himself a suite at the Airport Marquis...
荣谷正入住侯爵机场酒店套房…
...under the name Jamieson.
并化名詹美臣
He's there now. I want you to get that to bail bondsmen, bookies...
他到了，我要你把这消息告诉…
...assignment officers and snitches in County.
外围带家，奉派警员及线人
Anyone you can think of who'll put it on the street. Deploy a team at the hotel...
任何把消息外泄的人派人到酒店
...and personally check their coms every 30 minutes.
并每隔半小时收听无线电
Because maybe Neil will go for him.
也许尼尔会杀他
How're you feeling?
你感到怎样？
Hang up, but I'll live.
我会活的
He's here.
他仍在
Neil is still here.
尼尔还没走
I can feel it.
我可感觉到
For how long?
会留多久？
Seven, eight hours, maX.
最多七八个小时
What did you do?
你做过什么？
That was you?
是你做的？
I don't sell metal.
我不是卖金属的
Would have been okay, you fly out after. Now it's jammed.
计划本顺利但现时出了麻烦
We gotta go together.
我们要一起走
Those other people were with you?
那些人和你一起？
My friend, Michael...
我的朋友米高…
...he knew the risks.
他知道所冒的险
When it rains, you get wet.
身处险境便要冒生命危险
Get packed.
收拾东西
Why did you do this to me?
你为何这样对我？
Lt'll be all right.
不会有事的
Do you understand?
明白吗？
There's a Camaro at this address, Level D, Slot 18.
这地址D层18单位有一汽车
Here's some cash.
这儿有现金
When is it over?
此事何时了？
Twenty-two hours from now.
22小时后
- Then we get out of here clean. - When will you let me leave?
你何时会让我离去
Go now.
不知道
You want out? There's the door.
门在那边
Will you let me leave later?
你稍后会让我离去吗？
It will be different.
情况会不同
Do you even understand?
你不明白？
It's ready.
准备好了
This is my friend Ralph.
这是我的朋友洛夫
You didn't tell me you were...
你没说你已然…
Oh, my God!
天啊！
Where's Lauren?
罗兰呢？
She's at Lisa-Beth's.
她在碧芙家中
This has nothing to do with me. I'm sorry.
此事和我无关 对不起
What are you sorry about?
你对谁不起？
Sit down.
坐下
Don't you even get angry?
你不生气吗？
I'm angry.
我生气
I'm very angry, Ralph.
我很生气，洛夫
You can ball my wife if she wants you to.
若她想你干她你可干我太太
You can lounge around here on her sofa.
你可躺在她的沙发上
In her eX-husband's...
在她前夫的…
...dead-tech, post-modernistic, bullshit house...
高科技后现代主义的荒谬家中
...if you want to.
若你想的话
But you do not get to watch...
但你不能看…
...my fucking...
我该死的
...television set!
电视机
For God's sake.
天啊
Put the television set down.
把电视机放下
- I never cheated on you, bitch.
我没对你不忠
- Maybe you should have.
也许你应该
- I should have? - You're a party to this.
我应该吗？
I made Ralph fuck you because it makes me feel good.
我要洛夫干你因为这使我开心
Our situation is absurd.
我们的处境荒谬
Shut up, Ralph! Sit down!
住口，洛夫！坐下！
Why is it that I have to figure things out and eXplain them to you?
我为何要向你解释事情
I say what I mean, and I do what I say.
我的说话是认为的亦言出必行
How admirable.
多么可敬
- You bet. - EXcept none of it's about us.
可是没什么是和我们有关的
No.
是的
I may be stoned on grass and Prozac but...
我定是抽大麻或服兴奋剂迷糊了
...you walk through our life dead.
但你在我们的生活中犹如死了
Now I have to demean myself with Ralph just to get closure with you.
我要自贬找洛夫终断我们关系
Passports, traveler's checks, plastic.
护照、旅行支票、信用卡
The plane...
这飞机…
...charter terminal, LAX, Hangar 17.
在罗省机场包机站十七号机库
Call letters are 1011 Sierra.
确定密码是1011山岭
Touches down...
飞机会降落…
...holds for you five minutes, then splits.
等你五分钟然后便起飞
The plane will stand an FAA check. Filed a flight plan, the works.
飞机会通过航空局检查等手续
Where's Chris?
基斯呢？
He's gone.
他走了
What?
什么？
Said he's going on his own. Went to find Charlene.
他说去找莎莲，他走了
- Did you bring him here? - Yeah, I did.
是你带他来这儿？
What happened?
怎么回事？
It's a free country.
这是个自由国家
Check in with me at 9:00...
晚上九时联络我…
...everything is still cool.
确保一切妥当
All right.
好的
I don't know what I'm doing anymore.
我已不知自己在做什么？
I know life is short.
我知生命短促
Whatever time you get is luck.
能活多久是运气
You want to walk?
你想终断这段关系？
You walk right now...
你现在离去…
...all on your own.
是自愿的…
On your own you choose to come with me.
你自愿选择跟我走
All I know is...
我只知道…
...there's no point in me going anywhere anymore...
我无谓再到任何地方去
...if it's going to be alone...
若我会独自一人…
...without you.
没有你在身边
I got a live one.
我有个活的
I'll hold.
我会等
Show yourself.
让基斯看见你
- Do it. - Shut up!
住口！
Now, just one second at the window...
只需在窗前站一秒
...and it's all over.
此事便会了结
Hey, man...
朋友…
...you know any place to rent around here?
你知这附近有地方租吗？
It's not him.
不是他
It's not Chris.
不是基斯
Unit 2, this is Command.
是指挥部
Take him at the street.Check him out.
截停他和查看身份
He's John Peterson.
他叫庄彼得
Valid ID. Car's registered to...
有效的身份证，车辆登记人是…
...Bukowski, Gene.
布基赞
Ran it to DMV.
向运输署查核过
It's clean.
没有不妥
Let him go.
让他走
Roger.
知道
Thank you. Have a good evening.
谢谢，晚安
It's no-go.
不是他
Would you like a cup of coffee while we wait?
我们等时你想喝咖啡吗？
Yeah, that would be nice.
那会很不错
What do you got?
你有什么消息？
Nothing's happening.
没事发生
Hello, it's Vincent.
是云信
What do you got?
有何动静？
Nothing's going on. Waingro went for ice.
没有，荣谷去拿冰
That's it.
就这样
You know what?
你知道吗？
Neil is gone.
尼尔走了
Flying like a bird.
像鸟儿般飞走
How do you know?
你怎知道？
We still got bait!
我们仍然有诱饵
- Maybe some time! - What do we got?
也许仍有时间
What do we got?
我们有什么？
Bon voyage, motherfucker.
旅途愉快，杂种
You were good.
你很了得
I'm going to the hotel.
我到酒店去
I'm going to take a shower...
我会洗澡
...and I'm going to sleep for a month.
然后睡个昏天暗地
Here.
来
Come on.
醒来吧
Shit.
操
Motherfucking waste.
浪费生命
Assholes shoot themselves all fucking day.
浑蛋经常自毁
Not you, baby.
你不会死的
Not you.
你不会的
Where would she be? Her name is Lauren.
她会在哪儿？她叫罗兰
Lauren Gustafson, and she's supposed to be here.
古罗兰，她该在这儿的
I need somebody to help...
我要人帮忙…
I got you.
我抱着你
You'll be all right, I swear. It's okay, baby.
你会没事的，会没事的
Let's get a doctor!
找医生来！
Let's go! A doctor here!
我要医生！
- There's your mama. - Let's just calm down.
冷静下来
- Is she on any drugs? - I'm calm. No.
她服用药物吗？
Get a trauma surgeon and a vascular surgeon.
找精神创伤及血管医生来
I think she cut both arteries. I could hardly feel her pulse.
她割断两条动脉她没有脉搏
Her pressure's down.
她的血压下降
So is the respiration. You have to intubate her.
要给她插管
It's ready.
准备好了
When's the last time anybody saw her?
最后一次见她时是什么时候？
I don't know.
我不知道
Where did you find her?
你在哪儿找到她？
The bathtub.
浴缸
Give her large-bore normal saline.
给她注射大针管的盐水
Keep pressure on those bleeders.
紧按出血的血管
Give me two units, O-negative. Let's type and cross her for siX.
两公升O型血查出她血型和输血
Where is respiratory? We need more help. Get them down now.
呼吸专家呢？我们需要帮忙
Let's have X-ray ready for post-intubation chest X-ray.
准备插管后照X光
Your daughter's out of surgery and she's in the recovery room.
令媛已做过手术及在疗养室
Her vital signs are stable.
她情况稳定
The surgeon will speak to you in a few moments.
医生很快会跟你说
She's okay?
她没事吧？
She's doing good.
她很好
She'll be okay.
她会没事的
She's going to be okay.
她不会有事
Oh, my baby. Why did she do this to herself?
我的女儿，她为何这样对自己？
Look what she did. Look what she did to herself.
看她把自己怎么了
It's all right. It's going to be all right.
没事的，不会有事的
I'm here. I ain't going anywhere.
我在这儿，不会到别处去
Do you understand? I ain't going anywhere.
明白吗？我不会到别处去
It's me.
是我
Plane's in the air now. You're right on time.
飞机已在半空，你准时离去
I still can't find a driver...so that's in the trust.
仍找不到可信任的司机
One other thing...
还有一事…
...I gotta tell you.
我得告诉你
The guy you want is in the Marquis under Jamieson, if you still give a shit...
你找的人在候爵酒店化名詹美臣
...which I figure you wouldn't.
我看你不想找他吧
You figured right.
你说的对
So, so long, brother.
再见，兄弟
You take it easy.
保重了
You're home free.
你不用担心什么
Take it easy.
保重
What is it?
怎么了？
Nothing.
没什么
Home free.
了无牵挂
I gotta take care of something.
我得解决一些事情
Is there time?
有时间吗？
There's time.
有的
I'll be right back. Just leave her running.
我很快回来，让车子开动吧
Registration.
入住登记
This is room service.
房间餐饮部
A Jamieson ordered a BLT, and they screwed up his room number. What is it?
詹美臣要了食物但房号弄错了
- They're always doing that. - I know.
经常会弄错，
1735.
是1735号房
Thank you.
谢谢
Your attention, please.
请注意
We are currently experiencing a fire alarm.
现时响起火警警报
Do not panic.
不用惶恐
Do not take the elevators.
不要乘坐升降机
I'm staying here.
我留在这儿
I'll check the stairs. If there's smoke, I'll pull you out.
我查看楼梯若有烟便会要你走
What about her dad? Should I call him?
我该通知她父亲吗？
He's somewhere in the Sierras.
他在内华达山脉某处
And she chose you.
她选上你
She picked your place.
选你的房间自杀
It's not right, what happened to her.
这样做是不对的
No, it's not.
是的
Is there any way that...
是否有方法…
...it could work out between us?
可克服我们间的问题？
I wish I could say yes, you know.
我希望说有
But...
可是…
...in the end...
到最后…
It's like you said:
一如你说的…
All I am...
我沉迷于…
...is what I'm going after.
追捕我的罪犯
I'm not what you want, Justine.
我不是你想要的人
Go on, if you have to.
若你要走便走吧
I'll stay.
我会留下
I'm okay. I can handle this.
我没事，我可应付
Just be careful.
你保重
Call me here. Let me know you're okay.
给我电话让我知道你没事
Okay?
好吗？
Security. There's a fire on three.
酒店保安，发生火警
We have to evacuate all floors.
各楼层的人均要疏散
I can't leave here.
我不能离去
Why don't we just talk about this a bit, brother?
我们何不先谈一下？
He's here on 17.
他在十七楼
Look at me.
望着我
Look at me!
望着我！
LAPD! Don't move!
罗省警方！别动！
Put your hands on your head!
手放在头上！
Switch me to TAC 5.
将我转到五号频道
Casals...
卡索斯…
JJ...
JJ…
Drucker, JJ...
泽加
I'm in the lobby level by the stairwell.
我在大堂接近楼梯井
What have you got?
有什么事？
Teams are moving up the other elevators to the 17th-floor elevators.
有人乘另一升降机往十七楼
All out of commission because of the fire alarm. People everywhere.
因火警警钟响起升降机不能用
Fine. 10-4.
好的，知道
Let me have that shot.
把枪给我
Told you I'm never going back.
早说过我不会回狱中的
Yeah.
是的